权欲 前情提要...
Previously on Power...
我们初见时 你觉得我会成为什么样的人?
When we met, who'd you think I was gonna be?
纽约最大的毒贩
The biggest goddamn drug dealer in New York City.
我不认识任何满脸褶的 老毒枭
I don't know any old, wrinkled drug dealers.
他们不是死了 就是在监狱了
They're either dead or inside.
你从什么时候开始骗我了?
Since when do you lie to me?
什么时候开始对我有所隐瞒了?
Since when do you hide shit?
幽灵变了心
Ghost took back his loyalty,
你也是时候改变了
so now it's time for you to do the same.
我愿意为你改变自己
I want to change my life for you.
我不想破坏你的家庭
I don't want to break up your marriage.
你喜欢我陪你在身边 不是吗?
You like having me around, huh?
- 是的 - 我接受你的提议
- I do. - I want your offer.
- 600万买断 - 事实上 并不买
- $6 million to own it outright. - Truth is not for sale.
我发现你不忠的时候 我就把它给切了
The moment I detect disloyalty, I cut it out.
关于罗拉 你说的对
You was right about Rolla.
我很抱歉 事情会变成这样 幽灵
I'm sorry it turned out like this, G.
是卡南告诉你的 对吗?
It was Kanan, right?
这么多年了 你们关系还是这么铁
You were still tight after all these years.
我是你的朋友
I am your friend.
罗拉死了 你欠我钱
Rolla's dead. You owe me money.
但是你还欠我几条人命
And you owe me bodies.
你得保证 你杀人的时候 我儿子不会死
You make sure my son ain't dead when you do it neither.
出去之前 我要你杀了幽灵
I want Ghost dead before I get out.
我是你的朋友
I'm your friend.
我想我们该行动了
I guess we should get to it.
我是你的朋友
I am your friend.
据说今晚会下十英尺雪
They say we supposed to get ten inches.
我是你的朋友
I'm your friend.
杯子是空的
Glass was empty.
在罗拉的胃里发现了威士忌
The coroner found whiskey in Rolla's stomach.
不论是谁杀了他 都让他喝了最后一杯
So whoever killed him gave him a last drink.
干的漂亮
That's classy.
我听说你拒绝加入底特律的
So I hear you turned down the new Border Task Force
边防专责小组
in Detroit.
我猜你会调查到底?
Guess you'll be sticking around?
罗拉被谋杀是一条新线索
Rolla's murder is a new lead.
当然 但是随着洛沃斯在加州被起诉
Sure, but we have no money to follow it.
我们没经费再调查下去了
With Lobos being prosecuted in California,
他们已经要我们结案了
they've shut us down.
罗拉谋杀案是纽约警察局的案子
Now Rolla's death is officially an NYPD case,
作案手法和阿尼巴尔的案子相同
just like Anibal.
可能是同一个凶手
Might be the same hitter.
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
他还喝了最后一杯酒
He had a drink.
被枪击后 他直接从椅子
At the kill shot, he fell right out of his chair
摔到地板上
on to the floor.
没有打斗的痕迹 没有反抗的迹象
No defensive wounds, no sign of struggle.
你认识他认识人干的
You think it was someone he knew?
他没想到会被杀
And he didn't see it coming.
他信任那人
He trusted the person.
你觉得是那个分销商干的?
You think it was the distributor?
你认为是幽灵干的
You think it was Ghost.
没准你是对的
You could be right.
但是已经不重要了
But it doesn't matter.
这周末卡利就会起诉洛沃斯
Cali will have Lobos indicted by the end of the week.
是时候放弃调查了 牛仔女郎
It's time to let it go, Cowgirl.
我们还有新的案子
We'll get the next one.
我去倒点水
I'm gonna get some water.
不行!
No!
你会带走了床的温度的
Bed gets cold when you leave.
每次都是
It always does.
我好喜欢你这个样子啊
I like it when you're like this.
那天晚上你吓到我了
You kind of scared me the other night.
幽灵已经完成了我们讨论的那件事
Ghost did that thing we talked about,
所以我们现在和好了
so I'm all good now.
谁是幽灵啊?
Who's Ghost?
詹姆斯
James.
幽灵是...
Ghost is a...
昵称 就像...
nickname, like...
只有我这么叫他
just between me and him.
为什么叫"幽灵"呢?
Why "Ghost"?
我们小时候就发现这家伙走路"轻飘飘"的
We knew this guy "Breeze" when we were kids.
就像幽灵一样
He came up with Ghost.
他说那孩子会隐身术
He said the kid had the ability to disappear.
从来不知道他何时出现 何时消失
Never saw him coming, you never saw him leave.
不过现在他穿的他妈的高档鞋子出卖了他
Those expensive-ass shoes he wears now changed all that,
就他妈的咔嗒 咔嗒响不停
clickety-fucking-clack.
有天晚上我听到他的声音了
I heard him the other night.
他来过 对吗?
He was here, right?
我不知道你还醒着
I didn't know you were awake.
妈的 你早点说啊
Holly, you shoulda said something.
汤米 没关系的
Tommy, it's okay.
你可以相信我
You can trust me.
我和你说过
I told you.
幽灵有塔莎在身边
Ghost has Tasha in his corner.
她知道所有事 对吗?
She knows everything, right?
她会支持他
And she's got his back.
是的
Yeah.
我也这样做
Maybe I can be like that.
有个人在你身边 默默支持你
Someone in your corner, just for you.
- 杰米 - 安琪 最近怎么样?
- Jamie. - Angie, how you doing?
要是能见到你 就会好多了
I'll be better when I see you.
我也希望你现在就在我身边
Yeah, I wish you were here with me right now.
你知道的
You know,
在萨顿开派对那天晚上 我没什么事
I'm free the night of the Sutton place party.
几周前塔莎已经知道这个派对的事了
Tasha's known about it for weeks now.
我要她过去
I told her she could come.
是的 当然
Yeah, of course.
听着 安琪宝贝 我保证 都会好的
Look, Angie baby, I promise, all right,
我会改变现在的生活
I'm gonna change my life.
以后只有俱乐部 我的孩子  还有你
It's gonna be my club, my kids, and you.
我今天能见到你吗?
Could I see you today?
我要去看雷娜的演出 她扮演安妮
I've got Raina's play. She's Annie.
和你的家人在一起吧
Be with your family.
安琪
Angie.
我得挂了
I got to go.
# 可能在房子里 #
Maybe in a house
# 被大山所遮蔽 #
all hidden by a hill
# 她坐着在那里弹琴 #
she's sitting playing piano
# 他在那里付账 #
he's sitting paying a bill
# 也许是我忘了#
and maybe I'll forget
# 他曾对我的好 #
how nice he was to me
# 我又是多么的依赖他 #
and how I was almost his baby
# 也许 #
Maybe
- 你好 - 再次表示感谢
- Hello. - Thanks again.
你们好 圣帕特里克夫妇
Hi, Mrs. St. Patrick.
十分感谢你
Thank you so much.
- 唱的太棒了 - 妈妈 妈妈 妈妈!
- It was great. - Mom, mom, mom!
祝贺你
Congratulations.
- 嗨 最近怎么样?  - 挺好的 谢谢
- Hey, how are you? - Great, I appreciate it.
- 哦 天呐 - 唱的怎么样?
- Oh, goodness. - How was it?
- 你太棒了 小宝贝 - 她来了
- You were amazing, baby girl. - There she is.
我为你感到骄傲
I'm so proud of you.
我的大明星
My superstar.
爸爸爱你
Oh, daddy loves you.
你都把感动我哭了
You made me cry.
嘿 告诉你妹妹 她又多棒
Hey, tell your sister how good she did.
- 你太棒了 雷娜 - 谢谢你 里克
- You did great, Raina. - Thanks, Riq.
小姐 我有一个惊喜要给你哦
I have a special surprise for you, Miss.
你可以邀请四位女生和我们一起回家
You can invite four girls to come home with us,
而且她们还可以住在家里哦
and they can sleep over.
- 真的吗?　－当然
- I can? - Mm-hmm.
- 我想邀请谁都可以? - 当然啦 宝贝
- Whoever I want? - Yes, baby.
你们可以呆在一起 好好玩
You can stay up, have a good time,
看部电影
watch a movie.
去问问她们的妈妈 可不可以
Go ask their moms if it's okay.
- 谢谢你 - 别客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
真的吗 妈妈?
Really, Mom?
塔里克 我也问过欧文的妈妈了 好吗?
Tariq, I already asked Owen's mom if it's okay too, all right?
你问过了?
You did?
姑娘们来了 你们俩可以在你的房间里
You guys can be in your room while the girls have the den.
- 谢谢你 妈妈! - 不用客气
- Thanks, Mom! - Yes, you're welcome.
你现在最好回家 帮我一起组织这事
Now you better come home, and help me with this shit.
你不用现在就回俱乐部吧
You don't have to go back to the club right now.
这个大日子里 雷娜需要她爸爸
Raina deserves her daddy on her big day.
- 圣帕特里克夫妇 - 您好
- Mr. and Mrs. St. Patrick. - Hi.
您好
Hello, hi.
雷娜今天表现棒极了
Raina was excellent today.
她的确很努力
She certainly worked hard enough.
- 是的 - 谢谢
- Yes, she was. - Thank you.
不 该谢谢你们
No, thank you.
你们的慷慨捐助 会让新的操场
Your generous donation will get that playground finished
在几个月之后就建好
in just a couple of months.
我们都感到非常兴奋
We're all very excited about it.
你们应该感到非常骄傲
You both should be very proud.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
慷慨捐助?
Generous donation?
你看到她有多棒了 对吗?
You see how great she was, right?
哇 塔莎
Wow, Tasha.
- 你怎么了? - 我怎么了?
- What is wrong with you? - What is wrong with me?
我得回去把钱赚回来
I got to get back to work to make some of that money back.
- 这就是我的问题 - 宝贝
- That's what's wrong with me. - Babe.
雷娜 和爸爸说再见
Raina, tell Daddy good-bye.
再见 宝贝 我真以你为荣
See you, baby. Mm, I'm so proud of you.
宝贝
Babe.
还要再加点迷迭香
Needs more Rosemary.
这酒有点淡
And it's flat.
- 詹姆斯 - 辛西娅
- James. - Cynthia.
我在最后确认一下细节
Just checking in on a few final details.
没问题
Of course you are.
现在这味道对了
Now, that works.
- 我的客户们肯定喜欢 - 我也觉得
- My clients are gonna love this. - I know they will.
并且我希望 这只是
And I'm hoping this is just the beginning
我们合作的一个开端
for our working relationship.
我以前和你提过 现在我再说一次
I've told you before, and I'll say it again.
你的生意只不过是
Your business is just the springboard
我想缔造的夜店帝国的跳板
for the kind of nightlife empire I'm trying to build.
我相信你会成功
And I am sure you'll do it.
你是能得到自己想要的东西的人
You seem like the kind of guy that gets what he wants.
我希望你能保证明年的派对还在我这开
I want your word that I'll get this party again next year.
尽管想到能与你合作很令我心动
As tempting as the idea of spending more time with you is,
詹姆斯 你应该知道我保证不了
James, you know I can't promise that.
你当然可以
Sure you can.
我们计划明年
We're thinking of having the party
在巴塞尔艺术展办周末派对
at Art Basel weekend next year.
- 在迈阿密? - 嗯
- In Miami? - Mm.
准确的说 挖掘一下国外顾客的价值
Exactly, capitalizing on the international crowd.
斯特恩准备在滨海大道开分店
Stern's opening a club on Ocean Drive.
- 我们可能就在那办派对 - 当然
- Probably do the party there. - Of course.
纽约已经是鸡肋
We've done New York to death.
这里太冷
It gets so cold here.
一会会我就觉得四肢僵硬
I feel trapped after a while.
迈阿密很温暖 阳光普照...
Miami, it'd be warm, sunny...
新的开始
Fresh start.
一个新开始
A fresh start.
辛西娅・谢里丹签了派对的最终合同
Cynthia Sheridan signed the final contracts for the party.
再有客人吐在沙发上
Any of the guests puke on the banquettes again,
她就自掏腰包来维护翻新
she'll pay for re-upholstery herself.
合同都打印出来了
Have it in print.
真有趣
That's funny.
你没事吧 老板?
You okay, boss?
当然
Absolutely.
你看上去并不怎么高兴
Doesn't seem like it.
说到辛西娅 她有没有告诉过你
Speaking of Cynthia, did she tell you
明年派对会在迈阿密开?
next year's party's gonna be in Miami?
见鬼
No shit.
在西蒙・斯特恩的分店里开
One of Simon Stern's clubs.
怎么到处都有这狗杂种的店
That motherfucker's everywhere.
南海岸很抢手
South Beach is hot.
我在那做过几年推广顾问
I worked as a promoter there a couple of winters.
你在那还认识什么人嘛?
You still know people down there?
认识啊 怎么啦?
Yeah, I do. Why?
你们要乘热吃
Get your food while it's hot.
姑娘们 快来吃
Come on, girls, eat up.
每个人都有份
There's plenty for everybody.
- 女士优先 - 塔里克 停下来
- Ladies first. - Tariq, stop it.
拜托
Come on.
别忘了拿张餐巾纸 好吗?
And make sure you take a napkin, all right?
当心点 别把吃的掉在沙发上
Be careful, don't spill anything on the couch.
- 给我两个 - 拿好那个枕头
- Let me get two. - Get that pillow.
我从来没有为你做过这些
I never did anything like this for you.
我知道你为了这些孩子努力做得更好
I see you trying to do better by these kids.
是啊
I am.
我只是想要做个好...
I'm just trying to be a good...
詹姆斯去哪了?
Where's James?
他和别的女人在一块
He's with another woman.
早就和你说了那个夜店是个麻烦
Told you that club was trouble.
模特还是别的女人?
Some model or something?
如果真是这样倒好了
I wish it was like that.
肖恩告诉我她的名字叫安吉拉
Shawn told me her name is Angela.
被你说中了
You were right.
你现在开心了?
You happy now?
我留不住他
I couldn't keep him.
我当然不开心
Of course I'm not happy.
我还记得这种感觉
I remember how this felt.
你爸每次回家都会洗澡
Your father would come home, take a shower,
然后上床睡在我的旁边 好像什么事都没有
and get in bed next to me like it was nothing.
后来他回来也不洗澡了
Then he stopped taking that shower.
我和拉凯莎说过这事
I talked to Lakeisha about it.
我准备找个律师
I'm just gonna get a lawyer,
我肯定能获得孩子们的抚养权
and I'm sure I'll get custody of the kids.
拉凯莎太过简单没有城府
Lakeisha is as simple as two plus two.
你嫁得是个毒贩子 塔莎
You are married to a drug dealer, Tasha.
幽灵绝不会伤害我
Ghost would never hurt me.
伤害有好多种 宝贝
There are all different kinds of hurt, baby.
如果你今晚就必须离开你该怎么办?
What would you do if you had to leave tonight?
你自己有钱吗?
Do you have any money of your own?
合法账户的户主是我们俩
The legit accounts are in both our names.
我可以分到一半
I can get half of that.
我早和你说过
I done told you before,
你拿不到他的非法所得
you ain't got no legal claim on his illegal money.
到时候你拿什么过活
That's what you need to survive.
你得为自己好好打算
You've got to have a plan.
你要三思而后行 宝贝
You got to look before you leap, baby.
我有东西要给你 安琪
I have something for you, Angie.
杰米 别再送我礼物 别再送我内衣裤
Jamie, no more gifts, no more lingerie,
也别送我鞋子
no more shoes.
我只要你
Just you.
好 只有我
Okay, me.
我们这周末准备去迈阿密
We're going to Miami for the weekend.
- 什么? - 是的
- What? - Yeah.
我之前说过 我要在那开分店
I'm gonna open a Truth down there like I said I would.
我还以为跟斯特恩的生意还摇摆不定呢
I thought everything with Stern went sideways.
事实的确如此 所以我准备自己大干一场
It did go sideways so I'm gonna do it on my own.
坎托斯在那认识人
Kantos knows some people down there.
他会替我安排一些碰面
He's gonna arrange some meetings for me.
我想去那里看看租个场地
I'm gonna look at rental space while I'm there.
我需要你的建议
I want your opinion.
我想让你在我身边
I want you to be with me.
想想 海滩 阳光
Think, the beach, the sun.
- 一起醒来 - 一个新的开始
- Waking up together. - A fresh start.
那你和塔莎说你去哪?
What will you tell Tasha about where you're going?
出差
A business trip.
我希望你认真考虑一下我的提议 好吗?
But I don't want you to think about all that, all right?
陪我一起去
Just come with me.
陪我一起去迈阿密
Just come with me to Miami.
我愿意
I would love to.
- 再见 - 再见
- Bye. - Bye.
下课见
I'll just meet you after class.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hi. - Hi.
我们得小心点
We have to be careful.
这个真漂亮
That's so cute.
- 你喜欢吗? - 当然
- You like it? - Yeah.
我今天看到它 觉得和你很配
I saw it today and thought of you.
戴好了
Here.
我很喜欢
I love this.
嗯?
Yeah?
我们需要车子在机场接我们
Need a car to meet us at the airport.
我们住在枫丹白露酒店
We're staying at the Fontainebleau.
当然 我叫圣帕特里克
Uh, sure, it's St. Patrick.
兄弟 搞毛线啊?
Yo, man, what's up?
汤米?
Tommy?
嗯?
Yeah?
先生们 我为这戏剧性的绑架表示诚挚歉意
Gentlemen, I apologize for the theatrics,
但是你们政府盯得我很紧
but your government has been observing my every move.
所以我不得不小心为上
So I am gonna take every precaution necessary
隐藏行踪
to conceal my location.
除此之外...
Besides...
现在我们需要放松...
Now we all just get to relax.
我觉得如果我们没被绑起来
I think we'd relax a lot better
我们会更放松 头儿
if we weren't tied up, Jefe.
很好
Very well.
帮他们松绑
貌似你解决问题的办法
It seems like your plan to solve your problem
需要杀了你组织里的所有成员
required the killing of everybody in your organization.
我需要时间来找出来为此负责的人
Took some time to find the man responsible.
他亲自解决的
He handled that personally.
他是我的一个朋友 头儿
He was a friend of mine, Jefe.
我欠他太多了
I owed him that much.
好极了 幽灵 嗯?
Bravo, Ghost, huh?
那是个老顽固 伙计
That is old school, man.
就如同我的父辈
我们很相像
- 你有重建的计划吗? - 当然有
- Do you have a plan to rebuild? - Sure as shit.
我们已经联系到了RSK的新首脑
We're already in touch with the new leader of the RSK's,
泰诺人回来了
the Tainos are back in the fold.
大家齐心协力
Everybody's getting in line.
- 是真的吗 幽灵? - 是的
- Is that true, Ghost? - Si.
很好 因为从现在起
That's good, 'cause from now on,
我需要你来配送双倍的货
I need you to distribute double the amount of product.
我被背叛了
I was betrayed.
我在加利福尼亚的经营危在旦夕
My operation in California has been irretrievably compromised.
在局面被挽回之前
And until that situation is resolved,
我有货需要配送
I have product in the pipeline that needs distribution.
- 我们知道了 - 我们还没准备好 头儿
- We got that. - We're not set up, Jefe.
不 我们已经得到了多方联系
Oh, no, we got more than enough contacts
来加倍我们的输出
to double our output.
但是我们需要来组织工作 这需要时间
But we have to work out the logistics, which takes time.
我们得到了... 我们已经准备好了
We got... we're ready.
- 幽灵 - 嗯?
为什么你如此不确定?
Why are you so unsure?
除非我能保证配送
I just don't want to give you my word, Jefe,
不然我不想给你承诺 头儿
unless I can guarantee your distribution.
那样会很傻
真的很傻
而且很无情
我在给你提供一个很好的机会...
...去壮大...
...不仅仅是雇佣更多的人来扩大你的生意
...而且还要拉大你们和街头混混的差距
差距很重要
我要你专心于别的追求
如果你拒绝 那就会...
Saying no would be...
显得愚蠢
噢 我们不会拒绝的
Oh, we're not saying no.
我们只是需要时间来制定一个计划
We're just saying that we need some time to set up a plan.
来给你配送
To move your weight.
为你提供机会核准人员
Allow you the opportunity to approve personnel.
很好
Fine.
我会等着听你的计划
I will wait to hear your plan.
可以确定对你的...
Are we sure that the threat to your... hmm...
对我们的生意的威胁已经解除了吗?
To our business is over?
幽灵 你找对人了吗?
Fantasma, did you get the right guy?
幽灵?
是的
Yes.
好极了
我不得不说 我很欣慰
I have to say, I'm so relieved
我们能达成共识
that we were able to work this out.
要是今天不得不杀了你们 我会讨厌那样做
I would have hated to have to kill you today.
没事的
It's okay.
嗯?
Hmm?
把他们带出去
幽灵 我会等你的电话 嗯?
Fantasma, I'll be expecting your call, hmm?
我会打给你的
这太疯狂了 伙计!
That was bananas, man!
今早醒来的时候 打死我也想不到
Who would have thought when we woke up this morning,
那个狗日的居然会对我们做出这种事情来!
that crazy mother fucker'd do us like this?
不过我会严肃对待的 真的 我会严肃对待的
I'll take it though, for real. I'll take it.
翻倍我们的供货 量很大啊
Twice our product, this is huge.
刚才他妈的都发生了什么?
What the fuck was that back there?
"我不知道 头儿 给我们时间"
"I don't know, Jefe. Give us time."
他本可能杀了我们
He could have killed us.
如果我们搞砸了 那我们只是推迟了死期
If we fuck it up, we're only delaying the inevitable.
洛沃斯说什么并不重要
Don't matter what Lobos says.
双倍的货物意味着双倍的人员
Twice the product means twice the personnel,
双倍的曝光率
twice the exposure.
这正是我们等待的时刻
This is the moment we waited for.
危险也同样翻倍了 汤米
Twice the fucking risk, Tommy.
我们总是想扩大生意
We always wanted to expand.
现在 机会自己找上门来
Now, we ain't got to beg for it.
洛沃斯需要我们为他做事
Lobos needs us to move this shit.
你总是说"机会是运气加上..."
You always said "opportunity is luck plus..."
"准备" 汤米 但是我们之前从没有
"Preparation," Tommy, but we never moved weight
运过那么大的量
this big before.
我们得准备好 伙计
We got to be prepared, man.
我们得先想一想 好吗?
We got to think first, all right?
不能想太久 洛沃斯是不会等的
Can't think too long. Lobos won't wait.
等等 伙计
Hold on, man.
很高兴你终于搞清事情的轻重缓急了
Glad to see you finally got your priorities in order.
这是一件好事情 幽灵
This is gonna be a good thing, Ghost.
我要去见鲁伊斯 去获得支持
I'm gonna go see Ruiz, get it shored up.
我会把你半路放下来
I'll drop you off on the way.
- 快来 - 好的
- Yo, come on. - Yeah.
- 翻倍出货? - 是把所有的事情都翻倍
- Double the product? - It's double everything.
更大的势力范围 更多的敌人
More territory, more enemies,
你们要怎样在这种条件下生存?
how are you gonna survive that?
你的意思是 我们要怎样在这种条件下生存
How are we gonna survive that, you mean.
因为如果我运得多
Because if I'm moving more,
那么我就要靠你做同样的事情
I'm gonna be leaning on you to do the same.
一起让他妈的钱包鼓起来
Line both our mother fucking pockets.
我很感激 但是说实话
And I appreciate that, but let's be honest,
你们已经被攻击好几个月了
you've been under attack for months.
我们已经处理了 事情结束了
We handled that shit. It's over.
为了重建 你们得保护好自己
But you need to protect yourselves in order to rebuild.
除非你乐意那样做
Unless you're willing to do that,
索尔达多族如果找别人合作的话
than perhaps the Soledado Nation will be better off
也许会更好
finding itself another connect.
别闹了 鲁伊斯
That's fucked up, Ruiz.
就这个价格来说没人能比我们供得货更好
Nobody's getting you better shit than us for the price.
汤米 我的肺上缝了针
Tommy, I got stitches holding my lungs together,
因为罗拉的婊子由于醉酒而没刺中我的心脏
because Rolla's bitch missed my heart by a dog's hair.
如果我为你们做事得经历这些
If I'm gonna get into something like this with you,
我需要安全感
I need to feel secure.
你还是从弗罗里达拿到枪吗?
You still get your guns out of Florida?
我可以拿到更多的枪 但是得付款
I can get more guns, but they need to be paid for.
我们会付的
We'll pay for it.
从现在起 你为整个组织进口枪支
From now on, you import guns for the entire organization.
你赚的钱会比我们任何一个手下都多
You'll make more money than every other primera under us,
你的安全也会得到保障
and your security is guaranteed.
听起来不错 但是幽灵是永远不会同意的
Sounds good, but Ghost will never agree to that.
我的话还不够有分量吗?
My word's not good enough?
你来晚了
是火车晚点了 伙计
你他妈盯着看什么 混蛋?
What the fuck you staring at, man?
没什么 伙计 没什么
Nothing, man. Nothing.
放轻松
Relax.
喂?
Hello?
女巫 我要见你
Bruja, I need to see you.
诺马 现在不是胡扯的时候 好吗?
Nomar, now's not a good time for bullshit, okay?
我见到经销商了 是真人
I saw the distributor, Mami.
我看清楚了
你认识他?
不认识 你给我看的画像簿里没有他
Nah, and he wasn't in that book you showed me.
好的 我要你马上去找素描画家
Okay, I need to get you with the sketch artist right away.
不 我们得先谈谈 女巫 好吗?
No, we got to talk first, Bruja, all right?
证人保护
Witness Protection.
如果我指认这个家伙 那么我死定了
If I I.D. this guy, I'm a dead man.
在确认我是安全的之前 我是不会告诉你的
I ain't telling you shit unless I know I'll be safe.
诺马打了电话给我
Nomar called.
他昨晚看见了经销商
He saw the distributor last night.
弗兰基 我们可以结案了
Frankie, we could close this case.
他们正在把我们的文档运到洛杉矶去
They're shipping our files off to L.A.
满怀感激
With their thanks.
- 弗兰基 - 证人保护计划?
- Frankie. - WITSEC?
不 我不能给你诺马・阿奇斯罗的证人保护
No, I can't get you witness protection for Nomar Arcielo.
安吉拉 都结束了
Angela, it is over.
继续干活吧
Move on.
那个经常在外面的家伙在哪里?
Where's the guy who's usually outside?
哪个家伙?
What guy?
电话车里面的那个
The guy in the telephone truck.
- 你指使的? - 对 几个礼拜前
- You made him? - Yeah, weeks ago.
但是他现在不在那里
But he's not there now.
瞧 我们有一个资金问题
Look, so we're having a funding issue.
政府破产了 但是没人知道你在这里
Government's broke, but no one knows you're here.
你是安全的
You're safe.
卧槽
Fuck that.
我走了
I'm out.
祝你顺利找到blanquito
Good luck finding your fucking blanquito.
我要离开这座城市
I'm leaving town.
诺马 我会给你应有的联邦证人保护
Nomar, I got you WITSEC.
目击证人保护?
Witness Protection?
我上司今早刚批准的
My boss approved it this morning.
- 真的? - 是的
- Really? - Yeah.
但是你必须呆在这里直到我能找到警察
But you got to stay here until I can get the Marshals
带你去一个安全的地方
to take you into custody.
我必须和一些人道别
Nah, I got to say good-bye to some people.
我会让警察安排你和家人告别的
I'll arrange a farewell with the Marshals for your family.
在这之前 不要告诉任何人 可以吗?
Until then, don't talk to anyone, okay?
给我二十四小时
Give me 24 hours.
谢谢你 美女
鲁伊斯参与吗?
So Ruiz in?
- 他不同意 - 草泥马
- He wouldn't commit. - Motherfucker.
他想要给我们提供枪支
He wants to bring in guns for us.
这次我们提供财力
We put up the money this time,
他就会援助我们整个帮派
he straps our whole crew,
但主要问题是扩张
but the real problem is expansion.
我觉得应该去找塞尔维亚人和漂流
I say we go to the Serb and Drift,
找些他们的朋友帮忙
some of their friends.
加强北泽西和斯塔顿岛的防守
We get North Jersey and Staten Island on lock.
不用 他们有自己的手段去运输枪药
No, they got their own connect bringing the product.
为了诱惑他们 我们必须降低价格
To lure them away, we got to lower our fucking price.
不...
No wa...
或者杀了那个混蛋
Or we kill that mother fucker,
那我们就手到擒来了
and make ourselves the best option.
先让我把这个弄明白
So let me get this straight.
你说我们和鲁伊斯进行枪支交易
You're saying that we run the gun deal with Ruiz,
我们袭击那个主要连接点
we hit a major connect,
很可能会引发战争
possibly starting a war.
- 这就是计划? - 你还有更好方法吗?
- That's the plan? - You got a better idea?
你应该去相信我 幽灵
You got to start trusting me, Ghost.
罗拉那事我就做对了 是吧
I was right about Rolla, wasn't I?
我是你的朋友
I'm your friend.
一旦发现了二心
The moment I detect disloyalty,
我就会像治疗恶性肿瘤一样彻底根除它
I cut it out like a cancer.
将来的某一天你会有自己的组织 明白吗?
你生活在乡村
同时你的人马会承担所有的风险
你是对的 汤米
You're right, Tommy.
你是对的
You're right.
我没顾全大局
I got distracted.
接下来你要采取行动
And then you stepped it up.
如果你一直像这一次这样坚持的话
If you hadn't been about it all this time,
我们就不会走到如今重建的地步
we wouldn't be in this position to rebuild.
我早听你的话就好了
I shoulda listened to you.
咎由自取 你是应该听我的
Damn straight, you shoulda listened to me.
所以现在我在听
So now I'm listening.
你想和鲁伊斯交易枪支?
You want to do the gun deal with Ruiz?
我们有街头战士 然后我们就可以发展
We get street soldiers, then we expand.
我们有RSK 泰诺人
We get the RSK's, the Tainos,
我还有鲁伊斯做同盟 海地人 塞尔维亚人
I get Ruiz back in line, the Haitians, the Serbs,
甚至还有中国人
maybe even the Chinese.
筹集这些最快得多长时间?
How fast can we make this happen?
你同意 我立刻打电话
You say the word, I'll make the calls.
你不需要我的同意
You don't need me to say the word.
这次 应该由你去带领
I think you should take the lead on this,
去做一个领头人
be the authority on the streets.
你什么意思? 我们总是一起去做这些事的
What you mean? We always done this together.
我哪也不去
I ain't going anywhere.
但是如果我们要赚双倍的钱的话
But if we're making twice the amount of money,
见鬼 或许我应该再开一个俱乐部
hell, maybe I should open a second club
去洗白这些钱 不是吗?
to clean that money, hmm?
或许你应该
Maybe you should.
我要你在这里得到你应得的尊重
I want you to get the respect you deserve on the streets,
汤米 其实他们问的不是我的想法
Tommy, so people don't ask me what I think.
而是你的
They ask me what you think.
我们异口同声
We're two men, and we speak with one voice.
异口同声
Two men, one voice.
我喜欢这样
I like that.
在我们得到所有的承诺后 你就去安排
So after we get all the commitments, you make the calls.
告诉他们我们准备好了
Tell'em we're good to go.
尽快拿到其余的现金
Get that extra cash in our pocket as fast as we can.
汤米 还有一件事
Tommy, one more thing.
我们不能超出这个限度 好吗?
We can't expand beyond this, all right?
这大概是我们的极限了
Probably the most weight we can handle.
咱们走着瞧
We'll see.
哦
Oh.
- 你好? - 肖恩
- Hello? - Shawn.
爸?
Dad?
我需要你做点事情
I need you to do something for me.
悉听尊便
Yeah, anything.
你不可以告诉你的叔叔幽灵 汤米以及任何人
You can't tell your uncle Ghost, Tommy, nobody.
我要知道我可以相信你
I need to know I can trust you.
我需要让诺马得到联邦证人的保护许可
I need to get Nomar into WITSEC.
前几天夜里他看见了那个毒枭
He saw the distributor the other night.
他看见了幽灵 除非他的安全能得到保证
He saw Ghost, but he won't sit down with a sketch artist
否则他不会让素描画家画出幽灵的样貌的
until I give him to the Marshals.
好吧 通常不会花多长时间
Well, it usually doesn't take that long.
弗兰基不同意
Frankie said no.
特别工作组已经撂摊子了
The task force is done.
我让他躲在一个安全的地方
I've got him holed up at the safe house,
不过我必须拿到许可 否则他就要跑路了
but I got to get results, or he's gonna run.
我知道你那边有人
I know you have friends over there.
嗯
Mm.
你可以打个电话
You can make a call,
随便给他编一个理由
maybe shoehorn him in into another investigation.
团伙暴力犯罪 走私枪支弹药 儿童色情物品
Gang violence, gun possession, kiddie porn.
任何一个都能让诺玛获得联邦证人保护许可
Anything that would support Nomar's WITSEC application.
我为你通融过好几次了
I have bent the rules for you more times
数都数不清
than I can possibly count.
坦白说 我已没什么理由这样做了 所以
Frankly, my incentive to do so has disappeared, so...
他看见了幽灵的脸
He saw Ghost's face.
格雷格
Greg.
我打电话过去  看看他们有没有可行的理由
I'll call over there, see if they have anything current
去满足诺马的申请
where Nomar's information might apply.
我会尽力而为 事成之后
If I get them to do it, if I get them to do it,
请我喝酒
drinks are on you.
成交
Deal.
拿了些能让你高兴的东西
Got something to cheer you up.
她把这些东西还给你了 哼?
She gave them back to you, huh?
她的是她的
I got those for her.
这些是给你的
Bought these for you.
你一定很爱她
You must really love that girl.
这些可不便宜
These ain't cheap.
我想让我们成为一家人
I want us all to be a family.
你和霍莉和好 幽灵变回原来的样子
You and Holly getting along, Ghost back to normal.
哦 他变回原来的样子
Oh, he's back to normal.
是啊 全部恢复正常轨道
Yeah, totally back on track.
他现在知道什么重要了
He knows what matters now.
你是这么想的?
You think that's what happened?
认为他...
Think he...
是忘记了什么重要的东西?
Forgot what matters?
大概只是一分钟
I think maybe for a minute.
但他现在又恢复了判断力
But he's back in his senses now.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be okay.
一切都会像原来那样 T
It's gonna be like it always was, T.
与世界为敌的我们三人
The three of us against the world.
现在还有霍莉
Plus Holly now.
是啊
Sure.
我要走了
到那以后再联系你
要去多久?
不知道
给我张照片来想念你
爸爸! 还给我!
Papi! Give it back!
做完作业 然后就还给你
Do your homework, then you get it back.
我已经做完了
I did it already.
给我看看
Show me.
你能出来见我吗? 最后一次
晚上八点在公园
格雷格 听到后尽快回我电话
Greg, call me as soon as you hear anything.
我需要诺马被监护起来
I want Nomar in custody.
明天我就要登机了
I'm supposed to get on a plane tomorrow,
如果没搞定的话 我就要取消旅行了
and if we can't get it done, I should cancel my trip.
尽快告诉我
Let me know.
嗨 美人
Hey, Mamita.
哦 嗨 Paz
Oh, hey, Paz.
- 我忘记告诉你了 - 你要去哪?
- I forgot to tell you. - You going somewhere?
迈阿密
Miami.
他们要在工作上做些调整
They're gonna be doing some reassignments at work.
我要去南弗罗里达办公室那边看看
I'm looking at the Southern Florida office.
什么? 真荒谬
What? That's ridiculous.
这边也有事要忙
There's got to be something closer.
你的上司是女的吧?
You have a lady boss, right?
你告诉她关于爸爸的事了么?
Did you tell her about Papi?
我说了 但是...
I did, but...
这是出差 哈?
A work trip, huh?
好吧
Okay.
我是和杰米一起出去
I'm going with Jamie.
他想在迈阿密南海岸开一家俱乐部
He wants to open up a club in South Beach.
如果他这样做 也许我也可以去看看
If he does, maybe I'll see if there's a position
那边是否有我这个级别的闲置位置
at my level open in the Miami office.
我自己也不清楚
I don't know.
我们打算一起过周末
We're going for the weekend,
但我们想让我俩的相处更长久
but we want to make it more permanent,
所以迈阿密应该可以让我们这样在一起
so maybe Miami's how we do that.
或许他告诉你的原话是
Maybe that's what he's telling you,
因为他想一直干你
because he wants to keep fucking you.
杰米是爱我的
Jamie loves me.
他告诉我他打算去那里把事情都安排好
He told me he's gonna make things work.
我相信他
I believe him.
我知道你没法理解
你变了 安吉拉
This is changing you, Angela.
你居然当着我的面对我撒谎
You just lied to my face.
我撒谎 是因为我知道你不会支持我
I lied, because I knew you wouldn't support me,
是因为打心眼里 我觉得你根本就是
because deep down, I think you want me to be
想让我和你一样孤独痛苦
as alone and unhappy as you are.
我也许过得孤独又痛苦
I might be unhappy and alone,
但至少我不是一个小三
but at least I'm not a chilla.
你难道看不到 他正把你变成和他一样的撒谎者 骗子吗?
Can't you see he's making you like him: A liar, a cheat?
我告诉过你 杰米和我是相爱的
I told you, Jamie and I are in love.
我希望你为我感到高兴
I need you to be happy for me.
我不打算对你袖手旁观 眼睁睁地看着你毁掉你的生活
I'm not gonna stand by and watch you ruin your life.
那么我希望你把我房子的钥匙还我
Then I need you to give me the key to my place.
杰米现在需要一把 而你不需要
Jamie needs one now, you don't.
所以现在 我们走私毒品和军火?
So now we're running drugs and guns?
该死 根据我对于幽灵的了解
Shit, as long as I've known Ghost,
他绝对不会容忍走私军火这种事
he hasn't been cool with moving heat.
他同意了吗?
He agreed to that?
他同意 但是是从现在起 我无需再去询问幽灵的意思了
He did, but from now on, I ain't got to ask Ghost.
他信任我去贩卖毒品
He trusts me to make moves.
我在街上混 他洗钱
I run the streets, he cleans the money.
这样分工很好
It's all good.
哦 我等会儿再来?
Oh, should I come back?
不用 胡里奥马上就走
No, Julio was just leaving.
霍莉 这是胡里奥 胡里奥 这是霍莉
Holly, Julio. Julio, Holly.
- 很高兴见到你 - 我也是
- Nice to meet you. - You too.
全在这里了
It's all there.
洛沃斯会像以前一样 给我们提供火药
Lobos is gonna deliver the powder, same as always,
但我们必须想想 如何从Elizabeth那里搞到枪
but we got to figure out how to get the guns up from Elizabeth.
我会让维克多和达里恩准备好的
I'll get Victor and Darien ready to make the runs.
很好
Yeah.
他是给你干活的?
Does he work for you?
是的
Yeah.
哦 天呐 你闻起来真好
Ooh, God, you smell good.
非常好
That's nice.
该死
Fuck.
你欠我情了
You owe me.
非常大的人情
Big.
你朋友把诺马编排进去了?
Your friends got Nomar into the program?
他们正在去跟诺马面谈的路上
They are on their way to get Nomar now for an interview,
另外还有一个素描画家同行
and a sketch artist too.
谢谢你 格雷格!
Thank you, Greg!
真的很感谢你
Thank you so much.
这将会成为我们寻找的突破口
This could be the break we're looking for.
那么 你想来一杯庆祝一下吗?
So you want to get that drink to celebrate?
我不能
I can't.
我在等一个电话
I'm waiting for a call from a friend
是一个南弗罗里达办公室那边的朋友
in the Southern Florida office.
什么事 新案子?
What, new case?
一个和我同样级别的检察官因公离职了
A prosecutor at my level is leaving for corporate.
你知道该怎么打发洛沃斯离开
You know how you said to let Lobos go.
尽管那个诺马马上就要进监狱
Although now that Nomar's gonna be in custody,
但也许会有些不同的线索出现
maybe something can come of it.
等等 你说什么?
Wait, what?
你要去迈阿密?
You're going to Miami?
你父亲在这里 你说过你...
Your father's here. You said you...
一定有一个男的
There is a guy.
自始自终都在
Was all along.
是不是...
Is that...
是不是你这次要去的地方
Is that where you're going with this trip,
他也会一起去?
you're going with him?
不是那样的 格雷格
It's not like that, Greg.
你知道的 你完全可以承认
You know, you could have just said it.
- 不要当着我的面撒谎 - 我一直没撒谎
- Didn't have to lie to my face. - It wasn't a lie at the time.
- 我以前并不确定是否要和他在一起 - 那你现在确定了?
- I wasn't sure about him before. - Are you sure now?
我来
I got it.
哦 我来 我来
Oh, I got it, I got it, I got it.
我来 我来 我来
I got it, I got it, I got it.
你穿这个看起来真火辣
You look really hot in this thing.
这正是我要的目的
That's the idea.
火辣等同于暗示
More ass equals more tips.
你勾引得那些男人夜夜流连在你身上
You got guys all over you there, every night.
这是一份好工作
It's a good job.
我赚了很多钱
I make good money.
你现在跟了我
You're with me now.
你不需要钱
You don't need money.
告诉坎托斯你要辞职
Tell Kantos you quit.
从来没有人这样对我
I've never had anybody take care of me.
我对此并不适应
I wouldn't be good at it.
但是也许我能为你工作
But I could work for you maybe.
我们可以在一起工作
We'd be in it together.
鲁伊斯 很高兴你打电话给我
Ruiz, glad you called.
- 枪的事要尽快 - 滚他妈的枪
- That gun thing is a go. - Fuck the guns.
如果你今晚把这事给我做了
We could be blood brothers for life
我们可以做一辈子的生死兄弟
if you do this for me tonight.
我一定帮你 你加入我?
I do a favor for you, and you're in?
好的 那么你有什么要求 伙计?
Good, what you need, man?
我手下一个家伙 名字叫做诺马
One of my soldiers: name is Nomar.
他居然敢干我的宝贝女儿
Been fucking my little girl.
给她发他下面玩意的照片
Sent her a picture of his goddamn dick.
操他妈的
That's fucked up.
我会给胡里奥打电话派他去
I'll call Julio and send him over.
不 不要派任何拉丁血统的人跟踪诺马
No, don't send no Latino after Nomar.
如果他怀疑我知道他和伊莎贝尔的事
If he suspects that I know about him and Isabel,
他会去留神那些波多黎各人... 那种我一般会派遣的人
he'll be looking for PRs... Somebody that I would send...
但他想不到会有白人
But he won't be looking for a white guy.
- Tomas - 我明白了
- Tomas. - Got you.
我在哪儿能找到他?
Where can I find him?
- 出门? - 是的 生意上的事
- Going somewhere? - Yeah, business trip.
坎托斯在迈阿密有些关系
Kantos has some contacts in Miami.
所以我今晚就去选个地方租下来
So I'm going tonight to look at rental space
再开一间夜总会
for a second club.
- 再开一间夜总会 在迈阿密? - 没错
- Second club, in Miami? - Yeah.
坎托斯打算去那边经营那个俱乐部?
Kantos gonna move down there and run it?
我会去那边从头开始发展
I'll get things started there.
他负责经营这边的
He'll run things here.
哦 因为他有三个孩子需要照顾
Oh, 'cause he got three kids to look after.
塔莎 如果我也需要 那我也会照看孩子
Tasha, if this happens, I'll see the kids.
当然如果有必要的话 我也会飞回来再回去
I'll fly back and forth if I have too.
你计划多久了?
How long you been planning to go?
今天才想到的而已
Well, it just came up today.
我可以和你一起去
I could go with you.
姥姥能照顾好孩子
Big Mama can watch the kids.
这是夜总会生意上的事 塔莎
It's club business, Tasha.
你从来都不想去听这些事 不是么?
You don't want to hear about it, remember?
自从你开了夜总会
Ever since you've opened that club,
你就变了 幽灵
you've been different, Ghost.
就好像我再也不认识你了
It's like I don't know who you are.
我有试图让你理解 塔莎
I've been trying to tell you, Tasha.
但你没有听
You ain't been listening.
等我从迈阿密回来 我们需要好好谈谈
When I get back from Miami, we should talk.
她说了什么?
What'd she say?
她没说什么 我想她已经知道了
She didn't say much. I think she knew.
我们之间早就出现了裂痕 安琪
We've been growing apart for a long time, Angie.
你并不是导致这个情况的唯一原因
You're not the only reason this happened.
这让我感觉不太好
That doesn't make me feel better.
这样呢?
Does this?
我现在完全是你的了
I'm all yours now.
很快我就会彻底自由了
And soon I'll be totally free.
跟你说过我能办到
Told you I'd come through.
你说过 而且你做到了
You did, and you did.
- 我要新开个户 - 好的
- I need to open a new account. - Great.
We won't be pulling from anywhere.
明白了
I see.
我要一个支票账户和一张借记卡
I need a checking account with a debit card.
借记卡只署我的名字
One debit card, my name only.
- 能借你的笔用用吗? - 当然
- May I borrow your pen please? - Of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
所有银行账单都寄到长岛市的这个地址
I need all the bank statements sent to this address
转交给La凯莎 Grant
in Long Island City, care of Lakeisha Grant.
还有什么事吗 圣帕特里克夫人?
Is there anything else, Mrs. St. Patrick?
有 还有一件事
Yes, just one thing.
我老公 圣帕特里克先生
My husband, Mr. St. Patrick,
不能让他知道这个账户 好吧?
can't know about this account, okay?
答应我你什么都不会说?
Promise me not to say anything?
我当然不能说
I actually can't.
法律也不允许我说 所以我会保守你的秘密的
By law, I'm not allowed to, so your secret is safe with me.
亚历克斯 你真好
Alex, you're so sweet.
现在你能让我进去看看保险箱吗?
Can you let me into the safety deposit box now?
当然
Yes.
嘿
Hey.
- 抱歉 - 没事
- I'm sorry. - No worries.
我是伊莎贝尔 爸爸都知道了 他看到了你发的照片
Bruja 鲁伊斯知道我替你办事了
Bruja, Ruiz knows I'm working for you.
他要杀了我 请求支援
He's gonna try to kill me. Send help.
我去皇后区我姑妈家 派人来
谢谢
Thank you.
我爱你
I love you.
妈的
Fuck.
操操操操
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
希望尽快见到你
See you soon.
很快
Real soon.
Bruja 鲁伊斯知道我替你办事了
Bruja, Ruiz knows I'm working for you.
他要杀了我
He's gonna try to kill me.
请求支援
Send help.
格雷格 诺马被连累了
Greg, Nomar's been compromised.
我们必须立刻去皇后区
We have to get to Queens now.
嘿!
Hey!
你喜欢上小女孩是吧?
You like to fuck little girls, huh?
靠
Fuck.
鲁伊斯说要提你的老二去见他
Ruiz said to bring him your dick.
幽灵
Ghost.
你说什么?
What did you say?
诺马?
Nomar?
该死!
Shit!
我是检察官 安吉拉 Valdez
This is A.U.S.A. Angela valdez.
我的线人被刺伤了
My C.I.'s been stabbed.
我现在需要救护车和支援
I need an ambulance and backup now.
疑犯可能还在这个区域
The suspect might still be in the area.
别丢下我
放心 我不会的
- 谁干的? - 幽灵
- Who did this? - Ghost.
- 他去哪儿了? - 该死
- Where did he go? - Shit.
别离开我
不不不 诺马
No, no, no, Nomar.
别这样
Stay with me.
别闭眼
Don't close your eyes. Nuh-uh.
看着我 诺马!
詹姆斯 詹姆斯
James, James.
真是棒极了
This is great.
大家都玩得很开心
Everyone's having a wonderful time.
喜闻乐见
That's what I like to hear.
要不是为了整个迈阿密艺术博览会的事
You know, if it weren't for the whole Miami Art Basel thing,
我确信明年能让我的客户
I'm sure I could get my clients to bring this party back
还在真理夜总会开趴
to Truth next year.
你可能没有选择
Well, you might not have to choose to.
我们谈话之后
After you and I had our conversation,
我做了些调查
I did some research.
如果我说要在迈阿密开一间夜总会
And what would you say, Cynthia,
Cynthia 你怎么看
if I said I was opening a Truth in Miami?
好 如果你能及时开业
Okay, if you can get it open in time...
老天 我本不该这么说 就这么定了
God, I shouldn't be saying this... it's a date.
好的
All right.
玩开心点
Have fun.
霍莉 你留在楼下
Holly, I need you to stay downstairs,
招待主酒吧
and serve the main bar.
我宁愿在楼上
I'd rather work upstairs.
所有好人都在贵宾室
All the good people are in V.I.P.
照我说的做 好吧?
You do what I say when I say it, okay?
我不管你是否跟汤米上床
I don't care if you're sleeping with Tommy.
只要你不辞职你就是在给我工作
You still work for me until you fucking don't.
实际上今晚是我最后一天上班
Well, actually, tonight's my last night.
汤米不想让我再在这里工作了
Tommy doesn't want me working here anymore.
我要跟他一起从事你们的其他生意
I'm gonna work with him in your other business.
你要做什么?
You're gonna do what?
没错
That's right.
我们现在是搭档了 幽灵
You and I are partners now, Ghost.
你叫我什么?
What'd you call me?
老天爷! 老天爷!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
你没告诉别人
You ain't tell nobody
我今晚出来 对吧?
I was getting out tonight now, did you?
- 没 - 很好
- No. - Good.
因为我想给大家个惊喜
'Cause I want it to be a surprise.
你现在对我最忠诚了 对吧?
Your loyalty's to me first now, right?
是的
Right.
好的
All right.
我们走
Let's go.
安吉拉 Valdez
Angela Valdez.
你好 我是吉姆 McClure
Hey, this is Jim McClure,
你要求与诺马・阿奇斯罗共事的
the sketch artist you requested
素描艺术家
to work with Nomar Arcielo.
你好
Yeah, hi.
听着 关于那个...
Listen, about that...
他们没付给我报酬
They didn't pay my hours,
事关即将结案的案子
something about the case being closed.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你都没见过诺马 付什么钱?
You never met with Nomar. What hours?
不 格雷格・诺克斯给了我阿奇斯罗先生的号码
No, I got Mr. Arcielo's number from Agent Greg Knox.
我们打过电话
We spoke on the phone.
但我要见到他本人以获取更多细节
But I need to see him in person to get more details.
我只能画个草图
I was only able to work up a partial sketch.
发给我
Send it to me.
你有我邮箱吗?
You have my email?
我自己掏腰包 马上发给我
I'll pay for it out of my own pocket, just send it to me now.
吉姆my 很高兴再次见到你
Jimmy, good to see you again.
Penado警官
Officer Penado.
我不得不告诉你
I hate to tell you.
另行通知以前我们要关闭真理夜总会
We're gonna have to close Truth down until further notice.
- 多久? - 可能是一个月
- How long? - Could be a month.
也可能是一年
Could be a year.
这些事比较费时间还烧钱
These things take time and money.
保持联系
We'll be in touch.
幽灵
Fantasma.
我都要放弃你了
I was about to give up on you.
洛沃斯 我们加入
Lobos, we're in,
但不是双倍的 我要你所能发出的全部
but not for double the weight. I need all the product you can send.
所有的
All of it.
很高兴你克服了自己的犹豫
I'm glad to see you overcame your hesitation.
我有突发需求 要更大笔现金流
I have a sudden need for a larger influx of cash.
成交
We have a deal.
如果你能完成 就会有丰厚的回报
If you come through, the rewards will be massive.
- 如果完不成... - 我了解风险 头儿
- If not, well... - I know the stakes, Jefe.
任务艰巨啊
It's quite a large commitment.
我知道
I know.
我要成为纽约最大的毒枭
I'll be the biggest goddamn drug dealer in New York City.